PERSONAL INFORMATION:

FIRST NAMES: NHLAKANIPHO, MPILO, PAUL

SURNAME: NGUBO

NATIONALITY: SOUTH AFRICAN

LANGUAGES: ENGLISH AND ISIZULU

EMAIL ADDRESS: nhlakanipho.ngubo@umuzi.org /

mpilongubo07@gmail.com

ABOUT ME:

I AM A DATA ENGINEER IN THE MAKING. I HAVE EXPERIENCE IN DEVELOPING PYTHON PROJECTS. I LIKE THE EVER-CHANGING WORLD OF TECHNOLOGY BECAUSE IT OFTEN PRESENTS OPPORTUNITIES TO LEARN AND GROW AS AN INDIVIDUAL AND AS A TEAM PLAYER. I LOOK FORWARD TO WORKING WITH CREATIVE AND INNOVATIVE DEVELOPERS.

EDUCATION:

DURATION: FEBRUARY 2024 – STILL STUDYING

NAME OF INSTITUTION: UMUZI

TYPE OF COURSE: NATIONAL CERTIFICATE IN IT (SYSTEMS

DEVELOPMENT) NQF LEVEL 5

LINKS:

GitHub



DURATION: JANUARY 2021 – JUNE 2023 **NAME OF INSTITUTION:** UNIVERSITY OF PRETORIA

TYPE OF COURSE: BENG MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

(INCOMPLETE)

DURATION:JULY 2018 – DECEMBER 2020

NAME OF INSTITUTION:
BMW NORTHCLIFF AUTO

TYPE OF COURSE: AUTOMOTIVE REPAIR AND MAINTENANCE

NQF LEVEL 1

DURATION: JANUARY 2012 - DECEMBER 2016

NAME OF INSTITUTION: CORONATIONVILLE SECONDARY SCHOOL

TYPE OF COURSE: MATRIC CERTIFICATE

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

DURATION:JULY 2018 – DECEMBER 2020

NAME OF COMPANY:
BMW NORTHCLIFF AUTO

FULL TIME / PART TIME: FULL TIME

POSITION HELD: KEY ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:AUTO-TECHNICIAN APPRENTICE SERVICE ALL BMW VEHICLES

DURATION: JANUARY 2018 – JUNE 2018 **NAME OF COMPANY:** AUDI CENTER SANDTON

FULL TIME / PART TIME: FULL TIME

POSITION HELD: KEY ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:AUTO-TECHNICIAN APPRENTICE SERVICE ALL AUDI VEHICLES